This is Kinosaki Onsen, a small hot spring
town located in Hyogo Prefecture.
It is regarded as one of the best
onsen towns in Japan.
As someone who's enjoyed his fair
share of onsens over the years.
I was curious about Kinosaki,
so I decided to visit.
Over the next two days and one night,
I'll be exploring Kinosaki Onsen.
I'll be sampling local delicacies,
staying at a beautiful ryokan,
and soaking in a breathtaking onsen.
Come along as I explore Kinosaki Onsen
and share with you
why you need to visit this small but
charming hot spring town.
From Kyoto, it only takes
a little over two hours
to reach Kinosaki Onsen via direct train.
We jump on a JR Limited Express
train to Kinosaki.
We arrive in Kinosaki Onsen
just before noon.
Our first task was to find a lunch spot,
but we needed to deal with
our luggage first.
We just dropped our luggage off at
the Kinosaki Tourism Center and they'll either
keep it there or transfer it to a hotel
for a small fee of about 200 yen per bag,
which is great because then
we can just immediately
go and explore the town here.
We decided to head for lunch
and we found this place
called Mikuni that specializes
in steak and beef,
but specifically Tajima beef
is what we're looking for.
This is sorf of the special beef
that you can have in Kinosaki.
So we just ordered a lunch set
and it came out to like a
whopping 22,000 yen per person.
So it's definitely not cheap.
As we continue through town,
we start to notice more and more shops
selling snow crab.
Kinosaki is especially well known for
snow crab during the winter months,
thanks to its location near
the Sea of Japan.
It's one of the town's
most celebrated ingredients,
and something we'll get
more familiar with later on
After lunch, we keep things light,
picking up a few snacks as we walk,
including this Strawberry Daifuku.
Is it good?
The strawberry is good.
We also managed to grab  a box of Canelé.
We begin walking along the Otani river
This is arguably the most
picturesque part of Kinosaki.
The main river runs through the town,
lined with willow trees,
with small bridges connecting
both sides of town.
You'll also find plenty of shops
along the main street.
It's really a pleasant area
to explore on foot.
After exploring the town for a bit,
we head over to our
accommodation to check in.
All right, so we just checked
in at our hotel here.
I'm just going to show you guys
the room a little bit.
The room that we book is a sort of
Japanese traditional room
with tatami floors, as you can see here.
It comes with its own sort
of personal spa
that we wanted for our experience here.
With that said,
we already have booked a
Private onsen experience at this
onsen sort of facility
that I have on the third
floor of the hotel.
I've seen photos of it, it looks really
nice, so I'm excited to try that out.
But yeah, really nice hotel, feels more
glamorous than I expected really,
but looking forward
to experience everything this
hotel has to offer.
It's time for onsen, so I see
you guys over there.
We just arrived at our private onsen,
it's yet again a lot more than I expected.
Look at this, it is beautiful.
So, me and Lisa just finished our
private onsen experience.
The private onsen was called Gingetsu
which is their Japanese version.
They actually have two other versions,
I believe,
a Chinese version and
a Balinese version.
So if you want to book
the one that we had,
it's called Gingetsu, the Japanese one.
Yeah, overall,
it was a fantastic experience.
We head out for a
short stroll before dinner.
By this time, more and more people
are walking around in colorful yukatas,
most likely on their way to one of
Kinosaki's seven public bathhouses,
one of the town's main attractions.
It was now time to head
back to our ryokan
to enjoy a kaiseiki dinner
served in our room.
This video is sponsored by Saily.
If you travel a lot, you
know how annoying
it is to deal with SIM cards,
roaming fees,
or trying to find WiFi the
moment you land.
That's where Saily comes in.
Saily is an eSIM app that lets you get
affordable mobile data plans
directly on your phone.
No physical SIM cards required.
Whether you're visiting Japan
or road tripping through Iceland,
Saily's got you covered.
They offer data plans in over 200
destinations worldwide, so it's
easy to find a plan that
actually fits your trip.
Best of all, it's easy to get started.
Just download the Saily app,
choose the data plan you need,
and within a few minutes of
activating it, you're connected.
Ready to navigate, message, and explore
without worrying about data.
And if anything goes wrong, Saley's 24-7
live chat support is here to help.
If you want to try it out,
here's an exclusive 15% discount
on eSIM data plans.
Just download the SAILY app and use
the code allansu at checkout.
or you can scan this QR code to
get started right away.
Thank you, Saily, for sponsoring this video.
Now let's get back to Kinosaki.
It's going to end with us walking back.
Then we can take a hot bath.
Right, right.
We just finished dinner and
decided to jump in
our fully Japanese yukata attire
and decided to
head out for a little bit of
a sanpo, a little bit
of a walk through Kinosaki town.
Maybe check out some onsens.
There's some public onsens.
I believe there's like five,
Five? Isn't it five?
How many?
Seven.
Lisa confirms there's seven.
At least according to
the map we have here.
So there's seven public onsens
that you can go to
and if you stay at
one of the hotels here at Kinosaki
they're going to provide you with a pass
that allows you to go visit every
one of them if you want to.
I would say that it's
a little bit overkill, but you
can if you want to.
We're also very much as interested
in going into the town
and see how the ambience is
and everything like that.
We're on
the shuttle bus right now
that's going to take us to the town.
When night falls,
Kinosaki really comes alive.
The streets are softly lit by warm street
lamps and the sound of wooden sandals
echoes through the town as people walk
between the public bath houses.
Even if you're not planning
to visit a bath house,
it's worth wandering the streets
and taking in the atmosphere of the town.
And we are at the second onsen spot.
I think this is the final
onsens spot for us for the night,
before we head
back to our hotel and for a
good night's sleep.
All right, so early morning right now,
we are now about to check out
of our hotel here
at Kinosaki Onsen.
It's been a pleasure staying here.
The private onsen was incredible.
I would definitely recommend
if you're in Kyoto
and you want to have an onsen
town experience,
go visit Kinosaki Onsen.
It's a great place.
A lot of different hotels and
ryokans up here
that you can check out.
And also the cool thing about
these seven different
public baths that you can visit
if you're into that as well.
After checking out, we make one last stop
and visit the Kinosaki Ropeway.
We just arrived at the top
of Kinosaki Ropeway.
We are on the top station or top
of the mountain basically.
And there's like a little
coffee shop here.
There's a little viewing platform.
There's not a lot to do,
but you do get like a nice view
of Kinosaki onsen below.
It's rainy right now, as you
probably can see.
So the visibility is pretty
low right now.
A lot of clouds, a lot of
fog, but you know,
still trying to enjoy our time here,
our last few hours here in Kinosaki
before we head to Kyoto.
So right now just getting some footage
and then we're heading into the cafe
for a quick coffee break.
And then down to the town,
taking the train to Kyoto,
sucks with the weather,
but still trying to make
the most out of it.
Back down in town,
we make our way to Kinosaki station.
But before that, we stop
for Onsen Tamago,
eggs, gently boiled using
natural hot spring water.
We also managed to pick
up one last snack,
a Tajima Beef bun.
All right, that was my trip
to Kinosaki onsen.
I really enjoyed my visit to this
small hot spring town.
And if you're looking for a proper
onsen town experience,
that's near Kyoto, definitely
consider Kinosaki onsen.
The food and the private onsen
were the definite highlights
of this trip.
And I highly recommend doing
at the very least
an overnight trip
rather than a day trip.
You're simply not gonna
have enough time
to immerse yourself in the town.
So yeah, that's it for me.
Thank you for watching this video.
For more Japan videos,
stay tuned on this channel.
This is Allan,
safe travels,
and I'll see you guys
very soon.